[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 52, "question": "It's not like you haven't had a few awards -- two Emmys, two SAGs, a Grammy, now a Tony may be heading your way?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "like", "you", "have", "n't", "had", "a", "few", "awards", "--", "two", "Emmys", ",", "two", "SAGs", ",", "a", "Grammy", ",", "now", "a", "Tony", "may", "be", "heading", "your", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Well, I --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Oh, you do?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "-- I'll treasure that.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "I", "'ll", "treasure", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Is there anything you haven't won?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anything", "you", "have", "n't", "won", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "No, no Oscar.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "Oscar", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Does it actually work like that?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "actually", "work", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "It can work like that.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "can", "work", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "It's scary, though?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "scary", ",", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "It's scary.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "scary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vivian"]}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Yes, because there is a point later on in the play when my character, Vivian, is in incredible, incredible pain.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "because", "there", "is", "a", "point", "later", "on", "in", "the", "play", "when", "my", "character", ",", "Vivian", ",", "is", "in", "incredible", ",", "incredible", "pain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "I mean, were you a bit staggered, like many people, by the way the Republican race went in its rhetoric about women's issues?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "were", "you", "a", "bit", "staggered", ",", "like", "many", "people", ",", "by", "the", "way", "the", "Republican", "race", "went", "in", "its", "rhetoric", "about", "women", "'s", "issues", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "But has he done enough as president?", "question_tokens": ["But", "has", "he", "done", "enough", "as", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "You know, there are certain issues on which we can never do enough.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "there", "are", "certain", "issues", "on", "which", "we", "can", "never", "do", "enough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "If he gets reelected, where do you want to see a bit more grit?", "question_tokens": ["If", "he", "gets", "reelected", ",", "where", "do", "you", "want", "to", "see", "a", "bit", "more", "grit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Well, I certainly would like to see a bit more grit in terms of gay issues, in terms of LGBT issues.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "certainly", "would", "like", "to", "see", "a", "bit", "more", "grit", "in", "terms", "of", "gay", "issues", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "LGBT", "issues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "-- if he gets reelected?", "question_tokens": ["--", "if", "he", "gets", "reelected", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "-- I don't know if he's going to do that.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Two children?", "question_tokens": ["Two", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "And now you're going to be marrying a woman?", "question_tokens": ["And", "now", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "be", "marrying", "a", "woman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Christine"], "LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Did you expect what was coming your way?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "expect", "what", "was", "coming", "your", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "You know, when -- when news of Christine's and my relationship broke, there was this tremendous, you know, we were on the cover of two New York daily newspapers.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "when", "--", "when", "news", "of", "Christine", "'s", "and", "my", "relationship", "broke", ",", "there", "was", "this", "tremendous", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "were", "on", "the", "cover", "of", "two", "New", "York", "daily", "newspapers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "How do you wrestle with people who've got religious convictions about it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "wrestle", "with", "people", "who", "'ve", "got", "religious", "convictions", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Well, you know, I think that the thing is that gay people, that there are a lot of myths about gay people, that they are -- they're sick, or they're -- they prey on children, or they're harmful to children, or they're causing the destruction of the -- of traditional straight marriage.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "that", "the", "thing", "is", "that", "gay", "people", ",", "that", "there", "are", "a", "lot", "of", "myths", "about", "gay", "people", ",", "that", "they", "are", "--", "they", "'re", "sick", ",", "or", "they", "'re", "--", "they", "prey", "on", "children", ",", "or", "they", "'re", "harmful", "to", "children", ",", "or", "they", "'re", "causing", "the", "destruction", "of", "the", "--", "of", "traditional", "straight", "marriage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Are you as happy as you've ever been in your life?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "as", "happy", "as", "you", "'ve", "ever", "been", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "I am definitely as happy as I've ever been.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "definitely", "as", "happy", "as", "I", "'ve", "ever", "been", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Maybe the boyfriend will move in?", "question_tokens": ["Maybe", "the", "boyfriend", "will", "move", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "No, no boyfriend.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "boyfriend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "``", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "UH", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "What -- what would you like its legacy to be to American women, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "--", "what", "would", "you", "like", "its", "legacy", "to", "be", "to", "American", "women", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I think that \"Sex and the City\" showed that it was OK to be single, even if you were in your 30s, even if you were in your 40s, even if you were going to be single for the rest of your life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "``", "Sex", "and", "the", "City", "''", "showed", "that", "it", "was", "OK", "to", "be", "single", ",", "even", "if", "you", "were", "in", "your", "30s", ",", "even", "if", "you", "were", "in", "your", "40s", ",", "even", "if", "you", "were", "going", "to", "be", "single", "for", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "So, six months?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "six", "months", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "So we can spend pretty much every minute together?", "question_tokens": ["So", "we", "can", "spend", "pretty", "much", "every", "minute", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", ":", "CC", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "But why did you want to do this?", "question_tokens": ["But", "why", "did", "you", "want", "to", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "There were a lot of articles being written about, you know, single moms' sort of economic hardship and -- and sort of how they were supporting their families and the idea that a lot of women were having to help their husbands make money for the family and everything.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "were", "a", "lot", "of", "articles", "being", "written", "about", ",", "you", "know", ",", "single", "moms", "'", "sort", "of", "economic", "hardship", "and", "--", "and", "sort", "of", "how", "they", "were", "supporting", "their", "families", "and", "the", "idea", "that", "a", "lot", "of", "women", "were", "having", "to", "help", "their", "husbands", "make", "money", "for", "the", "family", "and", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Who likes it -- is it watched more by men or women?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "likes", "it", "--", "is", "it", "watched", "more", "by", "men", "or", "women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "It's pretty even, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "pretty", "even", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "And you know about this phenomenon, do you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "know", "about", "this", "phenomenon", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Is it -- is that basically what this is all about?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "--", "is", "that", "basically", "what", "this", "is", "all", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "WP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Yes, I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 364, "question": "What is it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "We saw that they were taking it down --", "answer_tokens": ["We", "saw", "that", "they", "were", "taking", "it", "down", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJR", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Yes, who did that?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "who", "did", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "-- what person decided, you know what, those need to be smaller, so I'm just going to --", "answer_tokens": ["--", "what", "person", "decided", ",", "you", "know", "what", ",", "those", "need", "to", "be", "smaller", ",", "so", "I", "'m", "just", "going", "to", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "I know, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "know", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Without any involvement.", "answer_tokens": ["Without", "any", "involvement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "You did?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "Yes, they're in my home.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "they", "'re", "in", "my", "home", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Where have you put them?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "have", "you", "put", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "I haven't decided exactly where they're going to go yet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "decided", "exactly", "where", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "go", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Do you think true love is out there, Jennifer?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "true", "love", "is", "out", "there", ",", "Jennifer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Waiting to lure you in?", "question_tokens": ["Waiting", "to", "lure", "you", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "At some point hopefully.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "some", "point", "hopefully", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Huh?", "question_tokens": ["Huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "You left me.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "left", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "What is -- what is Hollywood like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "--", "what", "is", "Hollywood", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "OVE HEWITT: I mean I think it's a great place.", "answer_tokens": ["OVE", "HEWITT", ":", "I", "mean", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "great", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Have you ever been lured into the Hollywood temptations that bring so many of your peer group crashing to the ground?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "been", "lured", "into", "the", "Hollywood", "temptations", "that", "bring", "so", "many", "of", "your", "peer", "group", "crashing", "to", "the", "ground", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "WDT", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Do you have sympathy for those that do?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "sympathy", "for", "those", "that", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "WDT", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "What about this whole obsession with size zero and skinniness?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "this", "whole", "obsession", "with", "size", "zero", "and", "skinniness", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "It's hard.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Do you like doing stuff like that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "doing", "stuff", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "It's fun.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Why do you think that is?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "that", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "What do you think that person is like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "that", "person", "is", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Are you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "If there are men watching this interview thinking, she's single?", "question_tokens": ["If", "there", "are", "men", "watching", "this", "interview", "thinking", ",", "she", "'s", "single", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "In one of the many dreams that you have -- we have already discussed this -- do you dream of a wonderful, white wedding and then having kids and everything else?", "question_tokens": ["In", "one", "of", "the", "many", "dreams", "that", "you", "have", "--", "we", "have", "already", "discussed", "this", "--", "do", "you", "dream", "of", "a", "wonderful", ",", "white", "wedding", "and", "then", "having", "kids", "and", "everything", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "I definitely dream of kids.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "definitely", "dream", "of", "kids", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Can you see how that could also, in the right place, be misconstrued as a mating signal?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "see", "how", "that", "could", "also", ",", "in", "the", "right", "place", ",", "be", "misconstrued", "as", "a", "mating", "signal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "IN", "MD", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Well, sure, I think that would be more like coming at you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "sure", ",", "I", "think", "that", "would", "be", "more", "like", "coming", "at", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "Yes, which is very exciting, right?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "which", "is", "very", "exciting", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Actually, I was going to ask you, it's a sad day for entertainment today.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "I", "was", "going", "to", "ask", "you", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "sad", "day", "for", "entertainment", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "Are you a fan of the band?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "fan", "of", "the", "band", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "I was, yeah, big time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", ",", "yeah", ",", "big", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "But it's a sad day, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "it", "'s", "a", "sad", "day", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "It is sad.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "sad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Were they?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "CD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Why can't I have both?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "ca", "n't", "I", "have", "both", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "I'll award your one now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "award", "your", "one", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Can I do that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "You can do that.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "Tell me why you would say something like that?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "why", "you", "would", "say", "something", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Well, usually when I play matches, yes, the match is in my hands.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "usually", "when", "I", "play", "matches", ",", "yes", ",", "the", "match", "is", "in", "my", "hands", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "But when you look at the incredible achievements that you and Venus have had, do you miss anything of that childhood that you had to sacrifice?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "you", "look", "at", "the", "incredible", "achievements", "that", "you", "and", "Venus", "have", "had", ",", "do", "you", "miss", "anything", "of", "that", "childhood", "that", "you", "had", "to", "sacrifice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "You know, when you're younger and you see the playground there, you see other things, you see your friends, or peers, going different places, and it's like, you know, you want to try that or you want to do that.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "when", "you", "'re", "younger", "and", "you", "see", "the", "playground", "there", ",", "you", "see", "other", "things", ",", "you", "see", "your", "friends", ",", "or", "peers", ",", "going", "different", "places", ",", "and", "it", "'s", "like", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "want", "to", "try", "that", "or", "you", "want", "to", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Venus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ":", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "Who would win?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "First of all, I definitely think it would be in -- go to a tie break, because we both have amazing serves.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "I", "definitely", "think", "it", "would", "be", "in", "--", "go", "to", "a", "tie", "break", ",", "because", "we", "both", "have", "amazing", "serves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "Who's more ruthless when it really comes to it?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "more", "ruthless", "when", "it", "really", "comes", "to", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "I'm really, really ruthless out on the court, but so is Venus.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "really", ",", "really", "ruthless", "out", "on", "the", "court", ",", "but", "so", "is", "Venus", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "You realize you just sentenced your sister to having all her limbs cut off?", "question_tokens": ["You", "realize", "you", "just", "sentenced", "your", "sister", "to", "having", "all", "her", "limbs", "cut", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "If it was down to limbs, they could take my limbs.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "it", "was", "down", "to", "limbs", ",", "they", "could", "take", "my", "limbs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "-- and you're winning, what do you experience?", "question_tokens": ["--", "and", "you", "'re", "winning", ",", "what", "do", "you", "experience", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "Well, when you're out there, you have to take the winners attitude, at least I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "you", "'re", "out", "there", ",", "you", "have", "to", "take", "the", "winners", "attitude", ",", "at", "least", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mohammed Ali"]}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "MD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 747, "question": "Who are the people, in any sphere of life, historically or now, that you really put on a platform?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "the", "people", ",", "in", "any", "sphere", "of", "life", ",", "historically", "or", "now", ",", "that", "you", "really", "put", "on", "a", "platform", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 748, "answer": "Well, I think I mean -- I never really got to see him fight, but I loved Mohammed Ali.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "I", "mean", "--", "I", "never", "really", "got", "to", "see", "him", "fight", ",", "but", "I", "loved", "Mohammed", "Ali", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 760, "question": "Forty-love?", "question_tokens": ["Forty-love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 761, "answer": "Not 40-love.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "40-love", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "Isn't that crazy?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "crazy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "-- in the middle of this.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 793, "question": "Isn't that amazing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "amazing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 794, "answer": "This is your private jet boudoir.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "your", "private", "jet", "boudoir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 810, "question": "You wanted to share that with the rest of us?", "question_tokens": ["You", "wanted", "to", "share", "that", "with", "the", "rest", "of", "us", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 811, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 824, "question": "How?", "question_tokens": ["How", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 825, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 826, "question": "How can you be single?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "you", "be", "single", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 827, "answer": "You know, I think it has a little bit to do with my career, and you know, just making some decisions that aren't the right -- yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "it", "has", "a", "little", "bit", "to", "do", "with", "my", "career", ",", "and", "you", "know", ",", "just", "making", "some", "decisions", "that", "are", "n't", "the", "right", "--", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 830, "question": "ORGAN: Do you know how many hearts broke all over the world when they read that?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Do", "you", "know", "how", "many", "hearts", "broke", "all", "over", "the", "world", "when", "they", "read", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 831, "answer": "Well, I hope not.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "hope", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 832, "question": "Can you now withdraw that Tweet?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "now", "withdraw", "that", "Tweet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 833, "answer": "No, I'm not going to withdraw that Tweet.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "withdraw", "that", "Tweet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 834, "question": "You're not going to never go out with another man again, are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "never", "go", "out", "with", "another", "man", "again", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 835, "answer": "You know, I'm not ready yet.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "ready", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 844, "question": "Doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 845, "answer": "It's not a fun space, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "a", "fun", "space", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 849, "question": "Are you a romantic by nature?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "romantic", "by", "nature", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 850, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 858, "question": "How many times would you say you have been properly in love in your life?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "would", "you", "say", "you", "have", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 859, "answer": "Probably just once.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "just", "once", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 861, "question": "Once?", "question_tokens": ["Once", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 862, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 870, "question": "It's bad, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "bad", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 871, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 878, "question": "I don't want you to put that on me?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "want", "you", "to", "put", "that", "on", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 879, "answer": "I'm just curious.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "curious", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "NNS", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 892, "question": "For the viewers' point of view, what are they called?", "question_tokens": ["For", "the", "viewers", "'", "point", "of", "view", ",", "what", "are", "they", "called", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 893, "answer": "They're -- our mission -- Missions is one of the companies that I'm owner of.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "--", "our", "mission", "--", "Missions", "is", "one", "of", "the", "companies", "that", "I", "'m", "owner", "of", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RBR", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 913, "question": "Do I?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 914, "answer": "You said some fighting words earlier on Twitter.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "said", "some", "fighting", "words", "earlier", "on", "Twitter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120504pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 978, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 979, "answer": "You will.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]